Yes, and of course, a huge, huge, huge
thank you to RO, who makes everything possible
and who tirelessly
shares his great knowledge with us –
knowledge that helps us solve our everyday problems.
Yesterday,
we dealt with the fourth level of the
program, the topic of
relationships. He believes in the perfect world,
that together we can
create this perfect world, and
that this perfect world begins and
ends with the perfect relationship, with the
deep understanding of
love. Okay, then there's
not much more for me to say. G.
Michel will definitely
give a short summary of what happened yesterday
so that we
can all easily get back into it. And then
we'll listen very attentively to the second part of
his presentation. And I ask you all
to welcome G. Michel Road for
today.
[Applause]
[Music]
Welcome! We wish you a
moving evening, perhaps with many
small and big insights,
and good attention. And yes,
thank you all very much
for
coming.
I'd like to repeat a little of
what we did last night.
Perhaps some of you were
here yesterday. Yesterday, we
talked about finding a new way to be a partner, a
relationship, etc.
Se secte dar a good relationship
arbeita
we
have new way GST
[Music]
one
asks why are you
then say quite honestly
and I have
decided Buddhism is right
has Buddhism possible good
relationship
to everything
is all things
fall apart and then they do
n't really understand Buddhism
yesterday the story told
how Bud
to last
night ag you have an obstacle to
enlightenment you can't without the
energy and
the energy of
[Music]
manism partner to have we very much
spiritual
fulfillment the man has a certain
energy doesn't
need energy
woman the woman also needs the energy
of
[Music]
man of
Buddhism
must that is like a mystical partner
[Music]
in the life of the
[Music] relationship
I like that
with a beautiful epic
relationship we great
epic
story and a love that saves the world
it is a romance that saves the world
and so we are trained
we are trained to find this kind
of partner
I believe that everyone in the world would like to have a partner
partner
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
then it falls apart
slowing
[Music]
not not
en al SPI no rlechen
[Music]
even before was I didn't have a
K as the first RA
not it's too loud for
me what I especially a d unbelievable
[Music]
many to
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
or forget
s happy but not really
happy in this
system it's all over
simply
partner WN
perfect
to have
WN you hurt yourself before
then try this
system new
system
promote every
age it's never too
[Music]
SP must
you don't have to talk to people you want to
dance then you
have in this
system we come to you
maybe in supermarket
[Music]
is the G
not
you how can
why does this system work
[Music]
gen I nsten minutes
sleep
we short question what
is sü h
I what
as a
SE they see that a chew toy
yes who is right the human or the
dog
[Music]
democracy if
I the dog gous the humans
gous at this
time which is it
a sch
Toy, you can
say every thing
in the world is
still everything in the world is exactly the
same out of itself
it is not what it
is that is not a STI V
STI does not speak to me
[Music]
that's not what the thing says when
I see a pen does
that have to do with my
ge when I use a tool
[Music]
my friend new partner a new friend
me
Yes
weles come to me
[Music]
seed to
plant if I have a good seed for
a watermelon and
throw it here we won't
grow the conditions have to
be right correct when you plant the new partner
or when you
improve your existing partner
[Music]
then you have to know how to
take care of Sam is not enough to
plant what
we will how we
grow well I
well it is not gen to plant a partner
[Music]
can
[Music] have have
we generation
[Music]
there are 2 teachers who came with me
they come from different
countries  They help me this seminar this
week,
one of them will teach us
meditations
so that your partner gets the right
qualities,
agricultural techniques for spiritual reasons,
many people
believe that if you
want money, then you have to give money away,
then the
problem is, oh, my
aunt is a very generous
person, she always gives money to others.
[Music]
business
[Music] business,
you just say it's
right to give money,
but my
aunt, this thought,
this question,
I wanted
JR to come to me,
company
[Music]
this
you have to help other people give even
more
[Music]
your whole
life, I said that means you plant
the
right things your whole life, you shoot the
right things, you have
millions, but you don't understand the process, you don't know what that is,
you don't consciously know the four steps.
[Music] that
and last week there were
many people,
I want
[Music]
religion, this
you should, this
fellow, you shouldn't live your life
without it, if there is
a new one that is gentle,
then he or she, we to
Come to you if there is
[Music] you should
try you shouldn't be lonely your
whole life
even with a husband
wife you have
perfect
[Music]
not be love
since last year
[Music]
I'm loyal to them
I
can Europe
[Music]
that makes it possible to see these photos
of
partners
trying doesn't say it
's impossible in this system you can
make impossible things possible what do you want
a sentence
[Music]
you can't
plant alone you have to find someone else
and you have to be together with them
[Music]
not
possible you have to find someone in whom the
G one
[Music]
must find someone who is very very one
can you
[Music]
think every
second
you think
plan one person
help you do
65 every
second thinking is very close to the
mind
planning oh I
know there's a
woman in
care children go to
visit her I
who I will go to visit her
I will
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
SP yes I
who I had the 20
Years 20 J
last
night her mother gave me a
[music]
big fl
wel
[applause] on
with 20
years now
today I plan for next
week
the
free very well
planted many
sen that is the difference between
this system and the
conscious
[music]
fantasize very very special
e before you
[music]
help the old woman please understand that
is the
secret
money doesn't go around can't
we haven't finished then you
can
is
principle
[music]
free imagination
big that makes the
difference
fast
P is the sentence what
go into
P I want a good one for life
[music]
have
not why
Sam are
small
big are very
powerful no
Kra they double in strength
every 24
hours a million
big they once every T
weeks spend an hour with
stories
[music]
on at
school I had the most beautiful
free whole
school if you pay very close attention you
can
what there is
I have
[music]
visit
you don't have to go every
day go once a
week T
weeks have D where I
live we  Go to
jail,
business, and
regarding every week
[Music]
the
direction isn't too
big, I'll be you
alone, I have
[Music]
Food is
food, you can write or film,
not so much
powerful meditation
[Music]
was when you think about happy things, think about
the good things,
process them again and again,
you can do 65 in a second,
all night
[Music],
think about the good things you did
for the old
woman, then
[Music], go all
night [Music],
aren't so long,
I
[Music],
many people
[Music], you don't have to do that,
just do step number four,
think about the good things
you did,
then sleep comes, wonderful for
you, happy
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
okay
[Music],
show how we
learn, how we learn something in the monasteries
[Music],
learn every
day or four hours,
discussions mixed with karate,
really,
and I should  A little bit of
SP, we'll show you how we do it
[Music]
then
here for 20
[Music]
minutes, asking very difficult questions from a
chair
[Music]
I'd like to hear some good questions.
Germany has some
difficult questions,
but
now
a question
[Music]
and then a new
partner comes along, you have to debate with me about
asking difficult questions, that's
selfish, you help
people, you don't
want to, you don't help from your heart,
that's like a
[Music]
business model, I help you if I
get something, I give you money, if I
get more money
[Music]
is the
following,
that's definitely not the
[Music]
getting a friend, that's not
the
reason not to
get a friend, yes, that's what I said, there
must be a reason other than
going to the nightclub to get a friend,
then I'd wear very pretty and
nice clothes to get a friend
[Music],
if that were the case, then
everyone who wears very pretty
clothes must be in
this room, what is it,
I think everyone can,
nobody who is in  Red from me can
tell me
what that's true, not even him,
and red clothes can say
friend is yes yes
[Music]
if you are a friend
musich
must be a good
[Music]
that
to we friend
let m do I understand that correctly if I
have a friend I have to plant a friend
this means that I in old
old D
[Music]
take care of you must do
something you must do something that has the same
quality as that
if you are lonely you have to go to the
[Music] lonely
only if I take care of a person
who I will
[Music]
yes I have already said
[Applause]
also that the be is friend
[Music]
to
[Applause]
[Music]
to everything I
want I didn't
say that can also happen if old lady
take care of Except I stranger
that's true
and to say what that could be that
's not
correct that you can
[Music]
if you go and take care of a person
two if you only do that
out of your own self only the friend you will get
[Music]
you tell me if  I take care of the old
lady, I only think about myself. I'll
get a selfish friend, that's
correct. The only chance there is is
that I make a friend. That's the
only chance to get one,
it's to take care of a lonely lady.
[Music]
And
That means I can say a good friend ca
n't
[Music]
Yes, when I take care of the old lady, I
think about it. If I succeed,
others will ask how I
did it,
then I can tell them that the
way to find a friend is to
try to be a good friend. [Music] But that's the way
I get a good friend, that
I make a bigger picture for the
whole world.
[Music]
That's right because they then
spread like a virus.
[Applause]
We now have questions and answers,
but I want to summarize what
just happened.
[Music] If you do
n't give
money, you
want to get money,
but you will
[Music]
V Ichol
I have
money payment, our company
quickly, and this book is spreading why
in the
Spirit al D
hil mus motivation in de ge
if I
manage this W I a fantastic
fre all
ask me years
[Music]
what's the name of the
website we
debted yesterday it's not the
website it's not the
after I planted it
I then I me he came to me the
use of the
fre H bemen
and that passes
virus all over the
world every eurochen
[Music]
too many
people
would it we in this world no one
live this
vision not
tive
compassion I want a world
where everyone
believes that the only love to
find is to give
this
[Music] please
ask the one or the one who has questions
that yes so
if
I if
I so if I
want to have one then I help a
lonely lady for example
what happens to two lonely ladies H
[Music]
If you look deeper and different
aspects in one woman
then maybe this one woman will carry
many different aspects within her
I accept the representation of
your story with the pen
and if I don't accept it the way you
've presented it then
the whole system works for me
[Music]
which part of the
presentation doesn't interest you  I like it, but we
say the system basically
works. It's not a matter of personal preference, but for me,
the
story isn't correct. For
example, if I were to reverse the story
and give the dog a bone,
then I couldn't use it to
write. The
second point would be
if I manage to write with the pen
while it's in the dog's mouth
[music],
then I can write with it. A
pen, a tool, a toy,
[music]
proof of my opinion that the
story isn't quite correct.
And the third proof would be that
even if the dog uses the pen as a
chew toy,
it's still a pen because the essence of a
pen is to be a pen, to write with it,
and if he were intelligent today, he
could also write with it
[music].
[music]
I'm going back to the [music]
question. We often get this question
from people who
think differently [music].
For example, if I
hold a [music] and I
let go, does [music] play a role, or
not? Or do I believe or
not do I have an influence of gravity?
We say the system is the same.
I recently [music]
many [music] and I don't have to [music] completely
on the ground.
falling and we say that the system
is the same, therefore
trying to
help others at a certain
time and you
get the question, and then you had a
few philosophical question marks.
The first would be to say that consensus
is not proof. If I get everyone in this room to
agree that it's a spoon, does that make it a
spoon?
Even if the dog comes in with me and says
it's a bone, does that not make it a
bone? What
I mean is...
[Music]
Here, it happens. We say,
unfortunately, we have no
control. Funny thing,
everyone has to think
and thinks
100% very strongly.
I
[Music]
I said that the dog is just too stupid. It's
simple. If it were more
intelligent, then it would...
But if you say that, then you're already agreeing.
If you say that, if the dog were more
intelligent, it would see a pen,
and that means that the
ability to see the pen
depends on the dog's ability to see... And
that's exactly what we...
[Music]
[Applause]
I've had that for a long
time.  I am
[Music]
and I also have to
protect my relationships with others.
Problem: I'm answering in German.
[Music]
said this example from the Buddha earlier: in every moment, in every second,
we make 65
impressions, and so it may be that in the
course of your life, you have now applied these principles.
[Music]
Possibly other actions have led to
a kind of obstacle.
[Music]
And
that you first have to clear these obstacles,
and in this case, that's a problem
with your
son. The sun
comes, the problems of the sun, and the
problems of the...
So you can repeat yourself in a sentence:
to find...
[Music]
What can I do? I ca
n't...
[Music]
teach the best... Canning... and... other...
Ken... selst
[Music]
Usually, they won't do what
you say they should do, but will do what you do,
how you
act. You, your
practice, your child... We will observe you and
try to imitate you.
[Applause]